

Grøfthøjparken 160, 4MF, 8260 Viby J
■ sofietrolle@hotmail.com
± 18/08/97

LANGUAGES

Danish - Native language English - Fluent

ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS

Art • Board games • Programming • Knitting • Design • Stand-up • Rock

WEBSITE sofietrolle.dk

LINKEDIN linkedin.com/in/sofie-trolle

GITHUB github.com/trolle18

CODEPEN codepen.io/sofietrolle

SOFIE TROLLE ÓMARSSON

Multimedia design student, specializing in frontend development

PROFILE

I am a multimedia design student with passion and a whole lot of drive. I am on my 3rd semester on Business Academy Aarhus, where I am specializing in frontend development.

Through my education, I have acquired many skills and competencies, such as:

Programming websites and web apps with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, API's, JSON, and WordPress.

In addition, I have with experience the Adobe programs: Photoshop, Illustrator, XD, as well as Figma and the Office package.

PERSONAL COMPETENCIES & PROPERTIES

Problem solver • Team player • Independent • Eye for details • Flexible • Thinking outside the box • Hard working • Ambitious • Quick leaner • Full of ideas

WORK EXPERIENCE

Distributor, substitute 2017 - 2018

FK Distribution • Part time

Office assistant & cleaning worker Feb 2016 - Jun 2016

Lemvig Tourist Center • Part time

Cleaning assistant 2014 - 2016

Dancenter Holiday Homes • Part time

EDUCATION

Multimedia design Feb 2021 - Jan 2023

Business Academy Aarhus • Academy profession program

HF Arts & Design Aug 2017 - Jun 2020

Aarhus HF & VUC • Upper secondary education

Folk High School - Main subject: Arts Aug 2016 - Jun 2017

Silkeborg Højskole • Folk high school